https://soundengine.com/content/6-privacy-policy

USD
Search:
Shopping Cart -
0
Item
Items
(empty)
Recently added item(s)
No products
Free shipping!
Shipping
Cart Total:
Total
There are 0 items in your cart.
There is 1 item in your cart.
Total products
(tax excl.)
Total shipping (tax excl.)
Free shipping!
Total
(tax excl.)
Continue shopping
Proceed to checkout
Home
Sample DownloadsLogic Pro EXS24 / SamplerPresenceKontaktKurzweil: K2x00 & CompatiblesKurzweil: Forte & CompatiblesEnsoniq ASR-XWAVHalionSoft Synth SoundsFM8Legacy M1Legacy WavestationVintage Synth SoundsAccess VirusEnsoniq ESQ-1Ensoniq FiZmOEnsoniq SD-1Ensoniq SQ-80Kawai K1Korg 01/WKorg M1Korg TritonKorg WavestationOberheim Matrix 12 / XpanderPeavey DPMRoland D-50Sequential Prophet 5Sequential Prophet VSYamaha DX7Yamaha FS1rYamaha MotifYamaha SY55/TG55Yamaha SY77/TG77Yamaha SY99Yamaha TX81ZField RecordingsFree Stuff
Menu
Home
Sample DownloadsLogic Pro EXS24 / SamplerPresenceKontaktKurzweil: K2x00 & CompatiblesKurzweil: Forte & CompatiblesEnsoniq ASR-XWAVHalionSoft Synth SoundsFM8Legacy M1Legacy WavestationVintage Synth SoundsAccess VirusEnsoniq ESQ-1Ensoniq FiZmOEnsoniq SD-1Ensoniq SQ-80Kawai K1Korg 01/WKorg M1Korg TritonKorg WavestationOberheim Matrix 12 / XpanderPeavey DPMRoland D-50Sequential Prophet 5Sequential Prophet VSYamaha DX7Yamaha FS1rYamaha MotifYamaha SY55/TG55Yamaha SY77/TG77Yamaha SY99Yamaha TX81ZField RecordingsFree Stuff
Home
>>
Privacy policy
Privacy Statement
Soundengine.com collects and retains data provided by our customers for the sole purpose of digitally delivering items you purchase from our website.
We collect and store the following data:
Email Address
Your email is required in order to provide you, after the purchase of one of our products, the link, and the instructions to download it.
Purchase History
We maintain a record of all your purchase, including date of purchase, the name of the purchased product and how much was paid, and IP address used to make the purchase.
Address
Your address is needed in order to provide you with an invoice (if requested) of the purchased products.
Payment data is not collected or retained by SoundEngine.com.
All payments for the purchase of our products is exclusively handled and processed through Braintree (a PayPal company) and PayPal. We do not collect, process, or retain your payment data.
We have no access to your payment account information.
Data Security
All data we collect are stored in a database, which is owned and operated by Zoho, a global internet services provider, and it's encrypted by HTTPS with an SSL certificate.
Cookies
We use cookies on SoundEngine.com website to save your navigation status.
Use of your email address
We do not share and we will never share your email, name, and address with third parties.
We periodically email you about updates, new products, and discounts.
You can unsubscribe at any time, but you will no longer receive any important communication, like updates of the purchased products.
To unsubscribe, please simply click on the link "unsubscribe" you can find at the bottom of our emails.
Your Rights
You can ask us at any time to permanently delete all your data stored (name and email address).
Notification of changes in the privacy statement
If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes on this page. This privacy policy will be governed by the laws of the United States and the State of California.
Contact Us
Call Us:
COPYRIGHT © 2020 SoundEngine.com. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
FOLLOW US ON:
